honestly
To be honest, you’ve never played with a government lease before, right?
To that extent
If you want to do it, won’t you be able to do it?
Just kidding, it was really, really fun.
Are you really going to work now?
Okay, okay.
When are you going home? You must be tired
Because there's no traffic, whatever.
I'm going to order something to eat. Do you want to eat it?
I said something was missing
There was no concession stand at the amusement park.
That's right
Somehow I thought it was more empty, me too
They don't often deliver for one person, right?
That's right
And a delicious house is a must
There is a minimum order amount
- Right.
Shall we go?
Then
- What?
- why?
why? Let's see
Working, working
No, what is it, take a look
Why are you so embarrassed?
- okay
- Look, look, look, look
Disgraceful, disgraceful
Hey
Aren't you going to work?
Good morning
Yes, good morning.
Hurry up and go make money
Yeah
I use the master bathroom.
It's broken there
Yeah
Have you seen my clothes?
- I saw it.
- I'm late.
When attaching the paste, show everything.
What are you doing now?
Don't tell me, multiplayer doesn't work
hello
well
The outfit is the same as yesterday, but neat.
I guess it's a laundry service
Because he is my son
Who ironed it?
Why so early today...
Let's talk
good morning, good morning
conductor, good morning
well
Why is it like that?
Do you have no brain?
How do you live without a brain?
you meet the director
Did you turn?
You can’t go to training? why?
I
I have some work to do.
Are you going to do this to each other?
You know I’m impatient, right?
I will support your tuition
We will support your housing expenses
Why don't you cover this?
There is a time for all these things
Deputy managers did not even receive applications.
That's right, much later.
I think I'll regret it
But?
What I need to solve now
There are times
I've thought a lot about it too.
Later, I missed the training in Chicago.
I feel like my stomach hurts, but
Do this here and now
If you can't organize it
There's a lot to live for
I think it's confusing
Seo Ji-woo again, again!
When I tried to cover it, I was scared.
I have a lot of water changes and my stomach is a bit weak.
The social department that I was so obsessed with
It was Seo Ji-woo when I was appointed.
He disappears
You almost died while drinking
This time, everyone wants to go
Seo Ji-woo again ahead of overseas training?
Are you doing that again, you idiot?
Because it’s not!
I have an important appointment
In your life
Whenever it matters most
Why does Seo Ji-woo hit the candle?
Seo Ji-woo, who is she?
You surrender every time
That thing that can't even plant a flag
Don't fucking call it love
Brother!
This time, I was doing some self-reflection.
Yes, now it's my father's company.
I decided to go in, yeah
Is your health okay?
Did you stop taking the medicine?
Now I have to show some filial piety.
Yes, I stopped taking the medication.
Yeah, come to your senses
They say you need to exercise a lot
So I
I know you go here, bro.
I came here for work, I
It's nice and quiet here
Ah, what is it, what is it
Seo Ji-woo has a man next to her, right?
That bastard who was photographed the other day
Even though we don't have any relationship
They live together
Living together?
They're openly flirting
They just told me about it
Brother, what is that bastard?
Is your sister-in-law living together?
No, but this is
Are you wondering if I'm the only one who applied this?
Yes? Do I feel like I was wronged?
Why do you care when you're divorced?
All you have to do is go your own way
Oh, well, the same road again
Because you can go
- What?
- Oh, that's it.
That's up to me, yeah
By the way, brother, that
Ah Ah-hye keeps calling me
Yes, I'll take it, so I'll give it a try.
Do you know what he says?
Pick up the phone or
I asked my brother to come visit me or something.
-Why me?
- So, what I'm saying is
What chance does he have to find his brother?
Is it because I lent that money?
Just because it's urgent
I gave it to you once
Well, it's not much.
Once again, indeed
Please contact me, I feel sorry for him too.
In your life
Whenever it matters most
Why does Seo Ji-woo hit the candle?
Seo Ji-woo, who is she?
You surrender every time
That thing that can't even plant a flag
Don't fucking call it love
How about tomorrow?
Can I see you?
who are you?
Yes, representative.
This is Lee Kyung-do.
I was supposed to see you today
Who?
Isn’t this CEO Seo Ji-yeon’s cell phone?
Seo Ji-yeon?
Seo Ji-yeon I don’t know
Where are you?
Where are you now?
cafeteria
I ate, I
CEO
Wow, let's eat together
You were eating alone like this.
Something delicious came out today, kid.
President, I think you’ve eaten everything.
I'll buy the coffee, okay?
Now, shall we go?
No, this restaurant was originally like this.
Is it okay to be cold?
Shall we wake up?
It's okay, it's okay
We have a promise now, a promise
Come on, wake up, wake up
Wake up, yeah
I have a meeting.
Was it on the right? Was it on the left?
Right?
Representative!
Are you okay?
Ah, yes
Please give me a change of clothes.
Yes, I will prepare.
yes
Give the CEO something warm.
It would be difficult to hide it now, right?
This doesn't make sense
Shouldn’t I go home?
How are you feeling?
If you consult directly with Jiwoo,
I think I'll be joining the company soon
That's good
It's good, I spent an hour
thank you
I guess it's Jiwoo
It's better to discuss it quickly...
I have to do it
But now...
I barely made up my mind
If you know I'm sick
You might be scared
It won't take long
My husband already
nursing home in canada
I'm looking into it.
You mean you know, right?
- But why...
- I told you so.
I'm not a good husband
It's not that surprising
Jiwoo needs to come to work quickly.
That's ironic
I…
Because I separated the two of you, back then.
Jiwooya
you shouldn't be here
Sister, I
I only have longitude
So you can't stay here any longer.
The amusement park rental hall.
I keep thinking of you
After such a long time
I don't know if I had fun
I live because I’m grateful.
Fine dining is different.
It's delicious
Ah, I'm full.
Why are you laughing? They say it's delicious
Menu price report
I was nervous because I was afraid it would be shit.
You have t-shirt trauma
I like it because I eat well without saying anything.
I have good friends
I like eating things like this too.
I had good friends
I have good friends at this age
I also go to the amusement park
Good
Hey, which point is…
Why do you call me a female friend?
woman person friend
I said something because the atmosphere was good
Are you holding on to the pod?
What should I say to my girlfriend?
You said you had something to ask?
If you're going to set me up like that
I won't ask
It's hardness
What are you so curious about?
My friend Lee Kyung-do
At that time
I'm not asking seriously
I think about it often, sometimes I wonder about it
What is it? take a break
then
Why did you go?
At that time in Yeonnam-dong
Where should we go?
Let's go somewhere cool
Jo Jin-eon came to the house at that time.
The day I met you
Jo Jin-eon looked at me
Cinderella said it was past twelve o'clock
Even if I endured it
It's only going to be infested with mice.
You two bastards, Mr.
then
when i left
I saw myself past twelve
this saturday
I'm going to go somewhere nice and eat.
Really? what? where?
I saw a Korean restaurant with a nice atmosphere.
Why? What day is it?
A day to eat delicious food
Something delicious...
Uh, mom
Dad?
how much?
Where is the hospital?
uh
Uh, okay, okay.
I think I need to go to the hospital now
I heard your dad was hurt a lot.
you are home
- I am now...
- Go quickly, go quickly.
Uh, sorry.
I'll go, I'll come back
All you have to do is live
yes dad
If you want to live, do it
That's fine then
Nothing special
Don't worry, Mom.
Uh, Jiwoo.
Uh, soo... He's in surgery.
don't worry too much
Eat well and eat well
I guess I'll have to stay here
Yeah, I'm fine.
Call me if you need anything
I'll leave the phone on
yes
If you're scared, sleep with the lights on
uh
What about your father?
They said the surgery went well.
But the fever didn’t go down
What is stable
I guess I'll have to wait a bit
I'm glad the surgery went well though.
Yeah
I have to go again
Uh, uh, yes, yes
Are you okay? Do you want to go to Seyoung’s sister’s?
No, I'll stay here.
I'm fine alone
It's okay, don't worry
I'm sorry
What are you sorry about?
Make sure your mother eats well
Oh, you eat well too.
your face is ridiculous
I'll go
Jiwooya
I…
Mom, it was hell.
I don't even know that
Mom and I paternity test
I wanted to try it
It's funny
A child born from an affair
He hates himself the most
My sister
Am I okay?
Was it okay?
When were you eight?
I found out
With mom and dad
I heard you say
In your ear while you sleep
I rolled up the toilet paper and put it in.
So that you can't hear anything
I wanted to never let you hear it for the rest of my life
I'm telling you with my mouth
Jiwooya
you shouldn't be here
Sister, I
I only have longitude
So you can't stay here any longer.
The look in your mother’s eyes that you have received your whole life
disgusting humiliation
That will also go to Lee Kyung-do.
That thing affects people.
Jiwooya
You have to live a better life
At the Vienna Little Theater
I am not the daughter of an actress who makes a living.
I have to become Jarim’s shining Seo Ji-woo.
that person's father
You were hurt a lot
very much
Lee Kyung-do
You don't have the strength or the time to look back
Wait a minute, huh?
Sir, BP
I feel like I'm falling
- Check again.
- Yes
So you can't stay here any longer.
The look in your mother’s eyes that you have received your whole life
disgusting humiliation
That will also go to Lee Kyung-do.
Could you please change the person in charge here?
It's a comfortable place to eat.
I think it would be very uncomfortable.
in the VIP room
Some part-time work
Isn't it?
Jiwooya
Why did you turn off your phone?
-Your phone is off.
- Jiwoo...
After the beep...
Jiwoo…
In the meantime, good stepdad
Thanks to my good sister, I lived in a luxury hotel.
Now I just…
Just Cinderella
sad ending
I did a lot back then...
Oh, that's why I didn't leave you
I just decided that I should die.
But actually dying is a bit much
It was scary
Well done
Well done, Seo Ji-woo
Thank you for living and not dying
Really, thank you so much
Hey, what are you good at?
You died and came back to life
Well, eat well and live well.
What's so good about appearing after divorce?
you…
Why are you still so stupid?
Pure and kind, I exploded
I'm sorry
I'm going crazy
What am I sorry about, you?
When you hurt the most
I wasn't there
I couldn't stay
then
my father
It's so bad
not you
It's me
When you have the hardest time
I'm the one who wasn't next to you at that time
Did you cry a lot?
It hurt a lot, right?
A kind crazy guy
I
I'm so petty
I am you
My studio apartment is too small
The bed is so old
The bathroom smells like sewage
Even if the scale on the sink dies, it won’t come off.
You…
Maybe you went
Just drink
That's what I think when I drink alcohol...
There's no answer
좁아 터진 생각 있잖아
그게 등신 같아서 또 마시고
나쁜 새끼
못된 계집애
하면서 또 마시고
네가
너무!
I miss you so much
Drink again
It's hardness
I hate the word shameless
The pronunciation is annoying
I hate you because you keep clinging to me
you are so close
Why are you smiling like this?
Then
It's hard to say stop now
So I hate the word shameless
Jiwooya
I was like that even when I was twenty.
Even now I am clumsy
How to make you comfortable
clumsy
I think your sister is very sick.
don't be scared
I am clumsy and clumsy
I'll try anything
whatever
Thanks to you, I came comfortably
Are you tired?
I like the car, so I drive it.
I need to call a taxi
uh
I have something to say
I should have done it a long time ago
Keep timing
What is it?
Would you like a cup of tea?
calmly
Just pretend it's not a big deal as much as possible, eh?
Is it your sister’s number?
To Jiwoo
I'd better say
I got a call
Oh, really?
No call back?
Uh, later, it's not urgent.
Lee Kyung-do
you with my sister
What do you need to talk about?
What should you tell me?
Jiwooya
Uh, tell me
Hello?
Yeah
Now?
No, I'm leaving.
Yeah
you have to explain this
I can explain
Come back and talk
uh
Are you angry?
Did I get the wrong day?
I also have Lee Kyung at home.
Perfect for a three-way meeting
Sister why...
What do you have to do with Gyeongdo?
No, I guess I can contact you.
Why am I the only one who doesn’t know?
I got caught
No, what is it?
Even if this is no big deal
I'm in a bad mood
Lee Kyung-do was very consistent.
If you’re still Seo Ji-woo
It's attention
Huh?
I asked you to catch me
I told you the flight time.
No, just in case.
I tried throwing it out of desperation.
I heard you ran right away?
He's a kid
Oh, really
Well, make me sit down
Did you ask me to persuade you to come to the company?
huh?
Somehow this person
I said I would do my best
before leaving the company
Stop drinking first, what was this?
Ha, it's my
Sister, well
I heard that Kyung-do packed his bags and came in.
- Really?
- 알콜릭 치료 전문이래, 자기가
이러면 내가 너무 부담인데
꺼져, 이 개새끼야
넌 인간도 아니야
어떻게 그런 걸 숨겨, 어떻게?
Just get out of my life
You fucking fraudster!
Was it fun?
I am immature and running wild
How funny was that?
The most sick person in the world
Stay here, Seo Ji-woo
Yeah, what is it like me?
you must have caught me
Will you please go out?
Whether I drink or whatever.
get out of my life
no
Uh, stop
Stop!
My dad is at this company
You know that I care so much, right?
I want to do well
I see the limit
I guess I was just good at studying
Seo Ji-yeon did well in her studies.
You like clothes
Yeah
Sister, I want to rest now
I want to see Roa too
Now you do it
I feel wronged
Sister, where does it hurt?
uh?
Just what
stress headache
A little brainy
I'm sorry
what are you
Sister, I
Because he was born out of wedlock
Jiwooya
No, listen, that's what I want to say.
That's my situation
When I step into the company
I thought it wouldn't work
In the meantime, Dad’s love, support, and encouragement.
You received it in abundance
I'm thankful for that
I really don't want anything more
I didn't even know my sister was having this hard time.
All this time, I was the only one thinking about myself
I'm so sorry
Not yet
I was going to tell my sister
I'm going to work
Do you feel like crying?
Are you impressed?
uh
Together at the company
The thought of going to work is overwhelming
Oh well, now that I think about it
There was nothing to be afraid of
You have a sister
Even if it's too much for me alone
If I had a sister, I'd do something in the middle.
What is middle?
I'll give wings to Jarim Apparel
My sister said that
I was wrong, I already...
Lee Kyung-do's fatal first love
I caught Seo Ji-woo.
Huh?
Is your first love really me?
uh?
- Uh, uh
- Were you never in middle school or high school?
I guess so
Well, you want me to catch you
I'm not the one to catch it
If you don't like it, it's okay.
It's like that
I had a good talk with my sister.
uh…
I heard you're going to work
They say it’s like Jalim has wings.
What have you got to say?
You said you had something to say to me?
Well, actually
My sister asked me to
You went to the airport, is that what you mean?
uh?
- Uh
-Why?
Are you afraid I'll be disappointed if I find out?
No, well, rather than that
Because you became my cause
I was able to get you to sit down
I didn't do it because you told me to.
Well, something like that.
Then, you and my sister...
It worked
It worked!
Hey, thank you so much.
So, you and me
You were thinking of me
Hey, I'm so impressed.
That's right
Uh, bro
The manager is completely crazy.
I'll take you there, what did you do?
Not moving
You only move when you break a glass.
brother
Did I do something wrong with the manager?
- why?
- I heard you don’t eat snacks.
Just say ‘This Kyung Do, I Gyeong Do’
I heard you chew it carefully.
I don't know
Shift me, quickly.
I really have a waist
I feel like I'm going to get crushed, really.
Yeah, I had a hard time.
I'll send you a taxi so go
Oh, that's right
You said you're not going to Chicago?
That's how it happened
No, but who would say that?
He's the guy who's going to kill me...
I'm going
Hey, why did you get involved with Ah Da-hye?
stop asking me
Nothing was involved
I've never seen it before!
Wow, that bastard
It's no joke, that thing
- Manager Jin
- Yes
This reporter came
Who called this fucking bastard?
Your Dongwoon Ilbo
Why are these damn people coming to my company?
me tomorrow
I have to go to an actor photo shoot.
What will you do if you don't wake up?
No, well, the manager
Well, I guess I should have forced myself to drink it.
Your sister probably drank it, right?
Hey, one drink becomes two.
How could there not be ten?
It's so sweet
Aww, I'm sick of alcohol
When will this stop?
I'm going
Sister, where are you going?
Please go in
Dujin Kim, you bastard!
Why are you here?
Ah, the head.
let's go
I'll get you a taxi
Open thank you
older sister
What does Jiwoo mean to me?
keep open
It's like a thick album
I can't even add a new photo I took
That's the photo that's stuck
I can't even take it out
Training in Chicago is a waste!
That's right, it's a waste
In a world where AI is attacking us
Is the metaphor an album?
Write a poem!
You damn analog conductor!
Are you ignoring poetry?
Is analog ignoring it?
You ignorant bastard.
Taxi, the manager catches it himself.
There is no cheesiness, there is always no, you
Why are you following me?
There's only one exit
Jump off, just!
The convening of the board of directors
Shouldn’t we do it?
former president
It's a clause in the will.
There doesn't seem to be any problem
Still, we need to get together and listen to opinions.
You'll feel uncomfortable
Why bother listening to those things you don’t like?
What about your sister-in-law?
Are you confident?
well
But you know
When I joined the company
I wasn't confident
A person who can say with confidence
Well, how much will there be?
Jiwoo, you'll do better than me
You just need to learn what you lack
you help me a lot
Of course I help, that's it, whatever.
I asked Jiwoo several times
It was a difficult decision
I barely managed to appease the child who said he didn't like it.
Because I'm sick
I think I came in with a lot of intention.
People are like that
Well, if you force it, the tension will drop.
Well, the results may not be good
Don't you ask me where I hurt?
Are you feeling unwell?
When did you have your health checkup?
It's so hard
Jiwoo, please be weak.
I just tried it once for no reason
Well, I'm glad it's a fatal accident.
I don't look in good condition
Take it easy
Health is important
Is your company important?
Yeah
thank you
- Intern
- Yes?
What is the difference between a friend and a female friend?
yes?
It's the same category, right?
Look, I have a female friend.
Let's say we met
But now at the end of the sentence
Saying ‘thank you’
I want to do it
So I say, ‘I have good friends.’
I did it
‘Thanks to you,’ is that what you mean?
yes
But it would be better there
Why don't you call me your girlfriend?
A little temper? Pint out?
What is my interpretation?
Now, that female acquaintance is a friend, a female friend.
Aren’t they both better?
If the woman tells the man
If you have some interest in it,
friend, female friend
From a woman's point of view, both are the worst.
That's right, that's right
There's no way you don't know
Why do you ask?
Are you awake?
Did you get caught?
Now take it
This is Senior Doojin’s favorite, right?
me first
It's good when you're feeling lazy
I will eat well
The tension keeps rising.
Right?
hello?
Joining party?
child, sister
Even though I didn't do it
Are you taking care of Jiwoo?
you?
You took care of yourself
Can you tell me in detail?
no! What time can I leave?
Yeah
Do I have to meet Seo Ji-woo again?
I have no choice but to meet again
When you become a managing director
Sister, can I buy it for free at your shop?
I'll ask my sister
Hey! If you are a managing director
I should be able to organize that.
There must be?
Is there one? Is there one?
- Mom
- Yes
But when do you eat cake?
Do you want to eat?
Because I don’t know when Jeongmin will come.
Let's just put in a candle
- Okay, then, uh, quickly.
- Yeah, yeah, uh
What do you plug in, you bastard?
The main character didn't come, huh?
You're always late, huh?
It grows beautifully, yes, beautifully
How are we Jiwoo?
When will this beauty fade?
You're so dazzling, I want to put eye drops.
Oppa, open up the lame comments
It's so consistent
You have a clear soul
You have to grow strong
Otherwise, I'll end up like Jeongmin's oppa.
- You bastard.
- Hey, you talk harshly.
No, it's my birthday
Thank you for throwing me a surprise party.
Well, should I just step on it like this? huh?
Is it mine?
But I really
Thanks to my friends, I laugh and live, huh?
Who takes care of my birthday
Now my mom doesn’t even take care of me
To be honest, this morning
I shed some tears
i am real
There are only you guys
Is it mine?
huh?
Today is mine, today is my day
Surprise party to celebrate my return to work
Iltassangpine, congratulations to you both.
Wow, double the joy, right?
That's right, that's right
This is why we fit in so well, right?
double
It's not working, stop it
I'll let you blow out the candles.
start
Then thank you
I haven't done anything like this before
It's been 3 years
My brother lives such a pitiful life.
They say marriage information companies are good these days.
Try applying
Jiwoo! Today is a good day
I keep doing it like this
Should I say that? uh?
That's right, my brother told me to eat it.
I also sent Korean beef.
You have to do well, Sorry
Huh?
when?
what? Why is your reaction like this?
Oh, really?
Hey, Dongwon
Are you old?
happy birthday
- My beloved Jeongmin hyung.
- Dear Uncle Jeongmin
happy birthday
One more time, one more time, one more time
Dear Jeongmin
happy birthday
- One, two, three!
- Two, three!
Well done! Well done
Now, birthday bread, now, birthday bread
Birthday bread!
okay!
Okay, okay.
How is the mood among executives?
Well, Seo Ji-woo
It won't be a welcoming atmosphere.
People who don't like it do it.
But again hastily
They are not people who express dislike
Because they are all people from the previous president.
Let's respect, what, that kind of atmosphere?
What can I say about this company?
Looks like some kind of group
We didn't come together to make money.
A group that follows my father-in-law?
I'm really uncomfortable with that.
Managing Director Kang
This is something that needs to be acknowledged.
Chairman Seo, from your youth
These are the people who were together
Chairman Seo is so
Because I took care of you like family
The mountain is so high
Can you get over it?
Now Seo Ji-woo is also appearing on the mound.
It's a step I'm so thankful for.
In a cave where you will be caught and eaten
I'm coming in on my own feet.
There's no way he's good at it
Have fun eating it
Is it crushed in a corner?
Then we have a better cause
You will have it
Everyone gets a share by selling their crops.
Let's disperse
When that time comes, we'll all stick to our side.
What year was Director Kang born?
suddenly?
Even if I don't do it, I feel like I'm 10 years younger.
You gently let go of your words.
Oh my
Excuse me
I guess I relied too much on Executive Director Choi.
Without even realizing it, I started speaking comfortably.
I'll be careful
from very small things
I think there is something called trust.
Our predecessor, never once to us.
I've never been comfortable speaking to you.
It may not seem like a big deal, but
That kind of thing creates respect.
I have to learn a lot
I'll raise a drink
thank you
Please go in
Oh wow, that old guy really
It's me
Uh, what's over there?
Try increasing the number of times
I'll prepare more medicine
Okay, just work a little harder
I have to finish it quickly
Danbi and I have a way to live.
Don't make mistakes
It's in front of the kids' academy.
Uh, right
Even so, I will go to the company
I was thinking of going once
Last time I did something
Be a little too sharp
Don't get me wrong
I'm just worried
I'm not saying what about you guys
I know
What are you guys doing?
Are you a friend? Is it some?
Or are you dating again?
friend…
I don't want to do it
Then we'll meet again
I can't say that.
Why?
If we break up again
Are you scared that you'll completely fall out?
No, that was a long time ago
Now why did Jiwoo leave?
Because I understand
No matter what situation comes
I don't think I'll fall out
But why can't you speak?
Jiwooga
I'm worried about what people will think
Because he got divorced
Does it come easily?
When you think of such low self-esteem,
I wonder what to do
Because I'm scared of maggots
You, you bastard who can’t make soy sauce, huh?
This is frustrating
Why don't you change like this? huh?
uh? I'm in the mood for swearing
This bastard cursed me
I was criticized openly
Hey, go home now.
Dongwon needs to sleep now, hurry up
let's go
Oh, that's right
Now
What is it?
gift for commuting to work
Why is the packaging like this?
Substance is important
It seems like you like walking barefoot.
When I looked for it, it was on the sole of my foot.
The blood spots were all there.
Our director also wears them.
Hey, that's enough, just wear them.
This is bad for blood circulation.
Fashion company managing director
How do you wear something like this
Put it on under your desk and wear it
Wear this when you're alone
Take a few laps around the office
They say the back pain is gone too.
Do you sell this?
Oh, it's happening again
It's really a gift for me
Real on this earth!
Was this the only one? sincerely?
Is the design a bit like that?
Should I draw a picture here?
Yeongdong Bridge won’t be blocked, right?
The identity must have been resolved.
- Yes
- Uh
Thank you though
I'll wear them well
uh
This is
When you first wear it
It's going to hurt a lot, but
If you wear them again
It’s good for headaches, and…
Good for back pain
Yeah, that, uh
Yeah
Going
Uh, uh
Yeah
- Did you call a taxi?
- Call me…
I should call you
Or what, drop me off at the subway station?
uh
Yeah
I'll go
Don’t cross Yeongdong Bridge
Let’s be in Gangbuk today
who
Appeal to Old Man Wolha
In the afterlife
We were born interchangeably
A thousand miles away I die
you are alive
my
This sad heart
You too...
I wish you knew too...
My second proposal is to you too!
What kind of bullshit is the second marriage proposal?
- Hey!
-What do you think of Jiwoo?
Selling your company?
Jiwoo took on all of this
Will I be able to endure it?
I like it when you don't go to Chicago
It's my ex-girlfriend's problem.
You can't do this in private.
current girlfriend
Mr. Jiwoo
I really wish I knew one thing
Gyeongdo always has 0 priority.
Jiwoo, I
I'll take you to a world you like